onlinerealgames.com 2012-12-05

# Privacy Policy at onlinerealgames.com

**1\. What personal information is collected ?**

* *The only personal information we collect about you is information which you provide yourself via forms on our  website, or our billing partner’s websites. (E.g. when you register with us, contact customer support, or sign up for membership).

* *No personal information is collected when you access the public areas of our website.

* *No personal information is collected when you play our Single Player Games. 

* *To play our Multiplayer games you will need to choose a username and password and provide a valid email address. To play games or use certain areas of our websites you will need to create a login account and choose a username and password. 

* *To subscribe for user membership you will also need to provide contact information including: your name, a valid email address, gender, home address, phone/fax number, zip/postal code, and country, together with payment details (such as credit card number and expiry date). 

* *To make use of our customer support service you will need to provide an email address and information relating to your query. 

* *To enable us to provide a better customer support service we may also ask you provide contact information including: your name, email, postcode and country, and to provide a number of security questions which we can use to verify your identity if you require assistance in the future. 

* *The questions and the answers you provide are up to you. You may opt-out of providing some of this information but it will limit the effectiveness of our support service if you do. We also sometimes collect and store other information by way of a questionnaire to assist our advertisers and partners, affiliates. 

* *You may opt-out of providing any information by simply choosing not to complete the form requesting the information, and hence choosing not to use that particular service.

 **2\. What other information is stored?**

We generate and store logs indicating usage of our site and activity in our games. We store 'save game' and 'game settings' information to enable us to provide a better games service in which your activities and achievements are remembered in the game.

 **3\. What happens to the information provided/collected?**

The information may be used:

* *To process your payment for game membership subscriptions.

* *To provide our customer support service, and to verify any claims or requests you make if you use our customer support service.

* *To enforce our terms and conditions, and prevent hacking activities against our site.

* *To send service announcements which contain important information about our service, our site, or your account. (For example an email reminder is sent to members if a subscription payment is due).

* *To aggregate information to generate anonymous statistics regarding use of our services. We may share this anonymous information with our partners, affiliates and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

* *We also use your personal information for our own internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can consistently improve our sites to better meet our visitors' needs.

* *To disclose information to the extent required by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or to enforce legal rights.

* *Any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. We may use this information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. These business, affiliate partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about various groups of our users, but do not receive information that personally identifies you.

* *Free Gifts, Discounts, Special Contests, Special Offers or Promotions. We may occasionally present a free gifts, discounts, special contests, special offers or promotion that is sponsored by us or another company. To qualify for entry in those free gifts, special offers, discounts, contests or promotions, we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s)or with others, we will provide a statement to that effect in the options with terms.

* *IP Address. All communication on the internet takes place between pairs of IP Addresses. Our Web servers will log the IP address that any connection is made from. We may use these IP addresses to help diagnose technical problems or prevent abuse of our systems or other site users. Your IP address may also be used to gather aggregate demographic data and target advertisements accordingly. We respect your privacy, except as specified above we will not sell, rent, or disclose your personal information to other companies. We will not use your email address to send you 'spam'.

**4\. A special note about children 18 years old and under**

* *onlinerealgames.com encourages parents to spend time online with their children. We urge parents to instruct their children to never give out their real names, addresses or phone numbers, without permission, when using the Internet. No information may be submitted to onlinerealgames.com by persons under the age of 18 without the consent of a parent or guardian, unless permitted by applicable laws.

* *If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to onlinerealgames.com, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below.

* *onlinerealgames.com will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 18.

* *Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after onlinerealgames.com deletes the information from its active database. 

**5\. Prohibition of Porn Images/ Videos and False information**

We strictly prohibit any uploads of Pornographic Images/ Videos and false information about a person other than the user. We do not hold any responsibility if any user uploads videos/ images/ ring tones/ data/ Virus/ Threat files that belongs to others.

**6\. Safeguarding your personally identifiable information**

onlinerealgames.com will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and onlinerealgames.com will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, it will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom. onlinerealgames.com transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

**7\. Archived Information**

onlinerealgames.com maintains archives of its web logs, database, and other systems and information. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived after onlinerealgames.com deletes the information from its active database (see the Web Logs paragraph above). onlinerealgames.com maintains archives for disaster recovery, legal and other non-marketing purposes.

**8\. Update Your Profile**

You can help onlinerealgames.com maintain the accuracy of your profile by notifying us when you change your name (only for games), zip code, and country of residence, age range, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from onlinerealgames.com, sign in to the applicable onlinerealgames.com site and then select 'update your profile' to change your newsletter preferences.

**9\. Acceptance of Privacy Policy**

Your use of the onlinerealgames.com site, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy. By using the onlinerealgames.com site, you are accepting the practices set out in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of any portion of the onlinerealgames.com Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

**10\. More information about cookies**

When you enter a site that utilises "cookies" your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie, provided your internet browser is set to accept them (most are by default). Cookies are text files that identify your computer to our server. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Cookies themselves only record those areas of the site that have been visited by the computer in question, and for how long. Users have the opportunity to set their computers to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. The last of these, of course, means that certain personalised services cannot then be provided to that user. We do not link the information. We just store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You can also disable the cookies from your browser and delete all cookies currently stored on your computer. For example, if you are using Internet Explorer, select "Tools > Internet Options" and then review your privacy settings or select "delete cookies".This may, however, prevent you from taking full advantage of the services that this website has to offer.

**11\. Sugessions/complements/comments**

We warmly welcome the sugessions, complements and comments relating the website readable content, graphics, features, games etc. from the users

**12\. Safeguarding your personally exclusive information**

Onlinerealgames.com will only collect personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve our legitimate business purposes, and Onlinerealgames.com will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided. In addition, it will take reasonable steps to assure that third parties to whom Onlinerealgames.com transfer any data will provide sufficient protection of that personal information.

**13\. Links to other websites**

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. We have no control over them. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Clicking on these links may also result in virus attacks in your computer system. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. However we recommend the users to load an updated anti-virus protection in the systems for safety.

**14\. Ownership Changes**

If the ownership of all or substantially all of the Onlinerealgames business, or individual business units owned by Onlinerealgames Ltd., were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the provisions of the current privacy policy.

**15\. Security & Return Policy**

Onlinerealgames do not store payment information on customers shopping on our website. We use highly secured third party payment services to protect the payment transactions and as such all information regarding the concrete method of payment, credit card info etc. is stored with the third party provides such as Paypal,CCAvenue etc.  
Please note that all sale and subscriptions on our website are final. Therefore you cannot return our products and we do not offer any form of refund as what you subscribe and pay for is access to Onlinerealgames.com and there hereafter offered services and content, used or not.
